[
  {
    "question": "I am a famous equation used to describe the relationship between energy, mass, and speed?",
    "answer": "E=MC^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am a process that occurs deep within the earthâ€™s mantle, where solid rock flows slowly over geological time.",
    "answer": "convection"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am a theoretical concept in cosmology that suggests the universe is expanding from a single, incredibly hot and dense point in the past",
    "options": ["A. The Big Bang Theory", "B. The Steady State Theory", "C. The Multiverse Theory"],
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am a popular law of physics that states that for every action there is an equal and opposite reaction",
    "options": ["A. Newton's First Law", "B. Newton's Second Law", "C. Newton's Third Law"],
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am that process that converts light into energy",
    "options": ["A. Photosynthesis", "B. Respiration", "C. Combustion"],
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am the smallest unit of an element that retains its chemical constituents",
    "options": ["A. Atom", "B. Molecule", "C. Proton"],
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am a celestial body composed mainly of frozen gas and dust, often referred to as dirty snowballs",
    "options": ["A. Planet", "B. Asteroid", "C. Comet"],
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am the force responsible for an object's resistance to changes in motion",
    "options": ["A. Gravity", "B. Friction", "C. Inertia"],
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am the process by which plants convert carbon dioxide and water into glucose and oxygen using energy from the sun.",
    "options": ["A. Respiration", "B. Photosynthesis", "C. Fermentation"],
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am the layer of the Earth's atmosphere that contains the ozone layer and protects us from harmful ultraviolet (UV) radiation.",
    "options": ["A. Troposphere", "B. Stratosphere", "C. Mesosphere"],
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am the chemical element with the symbol 'Fe' and am essential for the formation of hemoglobin in red blood cells.",
    "options": ["A. Iron", "B. Gold", "C. Silver"],
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am a fundamental force of nature responsible for the attraction between two masses and the reason objects fall to the ground.",
    "options": ["A. Magnetism", "B. Electricity", "C. Gravity"],
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  }
]
